Stephanie Galindo

stephanimatedworld@gmail.com | (209) 270-7748 | Stockton, CA 95212

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Self-motivated Web developer and Graphic Designer with a high level of experience working on multiple projects. Passionate and hardworking with a penchant for meeting deadlines. Interested in a role with a company promoting best practices and offering diverse customer projects.

WEBSITES LINKS

• Github:

https://github.com/StephanieGalindo10

• Web Developer Portfolio:

https://stephaniegalindo10.github.io/Bootstrap-Portfolio/

• Media Portfolio:

https://github.com/StephanieGalindo10

• Linkedin:

www.linkedin.com/in/stephanie-galindo-110194103

WORK HISTORY

Trilogy Education Services. Sacramento, CA

Teacher Assistant Full Stack Web Development | 05/2019 - Current

Support and assist students at UC Davis Extension learning web
development best practices.

- Assistant instructor for full stack software engineering.
- Lecture and be knowledgeable in web development technologies, including HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, MySQL, MongoDB, Express.js, React.js, Node.js, and more.
- Guide students through complex lessons, forming positive learning outcomes.

Amazon. Tracy, CA

Amazon Associate | 08/2017 - 05/2019

This position exemplifies the skills needed to properly select, package, and ship our clients' orders. In the Amazon Career Program to study Full Stack Web Developer.

 Managed team performance by training, mentoring, disciplining and motivating employees. Appeals Panelist For Rehire

Too Many Guppies Retail Store. Belen, NM

Co-Founder And Advertising Assistant | 06/2013 - 04/2018

Co-founder of Too Many Guppies a geek theme craft store. Created greek

SKILLS

Experienced in Product
Management, Retail, and Web
Development.
Languages: Fluent in English and
Spanish(Reading and Writing)

Technical Skills

- Programming Technologies: Experience t in HTML/CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Reactjs, and Bootstrap, MySQL, and MongoDB
- Version Control: Git and Github
- Visual Design: Adobe Creative Suite (Photoshop, InDesign, Illustrator)
- Video Editing: Premiere Pro and Final Cut Pro

EDUCATION

The University Of California, Davis Sacramento, CA 2019

Full Stack Web Developer
Certification: Web Development
The UC Davis Full Stack Coding
Bootcamp course covers theory
and application of web
development. Major
Technologies: MERN Stack:
MongoDB, Express.js, React.js,
and Node.js. JavaScript, jQuery,
MySQL, CSS, HTML

Google Analytics Academy Online 2019

Web Development

theme products. Responsibilities including marketing, graphic designer, provided administrative support, Inventory, and organized promotional events at Comic convention and on school campuses.

• Coordinated content, designs and periodic updates to the company Facebook and Esty store.

The University Of New Mexico. Albuquerque, NM Admissions Representative | 10/2016 - 07/2017 Responsibilities include the coordination, preparation, scanning, and retrieval of everyday documentation. Resolve problems and inconsistencies with data, perform limited data analysis, and prepare and generates various reports.

 Obtained documents, clearances, certificates and approvals from local, state and federal agencies.

Walt Disney World. **Orlando, FL**DCP Internship Retail Merchandiser And Food Service | 01/2016 - 08/2016

Stock all the merchandise, cashier, and log in all delivery for guest at home or resorts. Help with guest needs including activating Disney Magic Band with online app's. Food Service included giving guest their meals, counter stocking food, busser to keep the western environment for our guest.

- Completed Marketing Certification from DCP Classes.
- Maintained records related to sales, returns and inventory availability.

The University Of New Mexico. Albuquerque, NM Marketing Assistant | 07/2014 - 12/2015

Keep the marketing database up-to-date by inputting new data, updating old records and inventory. Marketing company products and services to customers. Design posters, flyers, web graphics for clients including local events. Photographer of product shots and fashion photographer.

- Edited, toned, captioned and uploaded photographs for advertising publications.
- Coordinated meetings between project members and clients to develop ideas, discuss progress and set goals.

VOLUNTEER

Volunteer Work

Organization: UC Davis Continuing and Professional Education Student Mentor Program

AFFILIATIONS

Women Who Code

- Member, Women Who Code, 2018 to Current
- Member, Phi Theta Kappa Honor Society
- Member, Women in Web Dev, 2019 to Current

Awarded for successfully completing the course "Google Analytics for Beginners"

 Awarded Certificate of Completion

Amazon Web Services : Loft San Francisco, CA 2019

Amazon Sumerian: Build AR & VR Applications BootCamp: Amazon Web Services

The University Of New Mexico Albuquerque, NM 2015

Bachelor Of Applied Science In Media Arts: Media Arts

- Member of Phi Theta Kappa Honor Society
- Graduated with 3.9 GPA

The University Of New Mexico Los Lunas, NM 2014

Associate's Degree: Digital Communications And Multimedia With Animation

- Member of Phi Theta Kappa Honor Society
- Graduated with 3.9 GPA

PROJECTS

Expense Tracker: March 2019
This App allow user to keep track of their everyday expenses so they can manage their budget.
Technologies used HTML,CSS, and JavaScript

Silent Hill Clicky-Application: January 2019

The app should keep track of the user's score. Every time an image is clicked, the images rendered to the page should shuffle themselves in a random order. Technologies used HTML,CSS, Bootstrap and Reactjs

Trivia Game Application:
December 2018
A Trivia game the player will have a limited amount of time to finish the quiz. The game ends when the time runs out.
Technologies used HTML,CSS, Bootstrap and JavaScript